{
    "subject": "resource/Charlene_(song)",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/So_So_Def_Recordings",
    "human_readable": "Charlene is released by So So Def Recordings.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752257466316223,
            "question": "When was Charlene released by So So Def Recordings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.842058002948761,
            "question": "Who was released by So So Def Recordings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.790335476398468,
            "question": "What happened to Charlene's contract with So So Def Recordings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7537133693695068,
            "question": "Which record label released Charlene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7409400939941406,
            "question": "Was Charlene ever signed to another label besides So So Def Recordings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7209500074386597,
            "question": "Is there any information about Charlene's future plans after leaving So So Def Recordings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6460811495780945,
            "question": "What is the name of the record label that released Charlene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5648753643035889,
            "question": "Is Charlene signed to a record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48898646235466003,
            "question": "Does Charlene have a new record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4139921963214874,
            "question": "What genre of music does Charlene make?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charlene is released by So So Def Recordings.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1180_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Charlene have a new record label?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1180_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Charlene signed to a record label?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1180_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the record label that released Charlene?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1180_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1180_42.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention Anthony Hamilton's album \"Comin' from Where I'm From\" (2003) and its lead single \"Charlene\", but they do not explicitly state that the song was released by So So Def Recordings.\n* However, one of the documents mentions Jermaine Dupri's So So Def Recordings as a record label associated with various artists, including Anthony Hamilton.\n* Another document mentions that Anthony Hamilton signed to Jermaine Dupri's So So Def Recordings prior to the release of \"Comin' from Where I'm From\".\n\nBased on this information, it is likely that Charlene was released by So So Def Recordings, but the documents do not provide a definitive proof.\n\nTherefore, my answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information from the document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1180/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt states that the song \"Charlene\" by Anthony Hamilton was released under the labels So-So Def, Zomba, and Arista. This supports the statement that \"Charlene\" is released by So So Def Recordings."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}